<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Machine Learning</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="rate_it">Rate it</string>
    <string name="rate_our_app">Rate our App</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="ask_later">Later</string>
    <string name="rate_msg">You are a Machine Learning Junkie! If you like our app, please take a moment to rate it!</string>

    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>

    <string name="intro_slide_1_title">Hello Geek!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_1_desc">The easiest way to learn Machine Learning gives you this app!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_2_title">Up for a challenge?</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_2_desc">You can have a better score if you are systematic and work hard!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_3_title">Like badges?</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_3_desc">We created specially for you a set of badges which are given only to the best of the best!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_4_title">Issac Asimov once said</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_4_desc">"Any teacher that can be replaced by a computer should be replaced by a computer."</string>



    <string name="page_1_1_definition">\"<b>Machine Learning:</b> Field of study that gives computers the ability to learn without being explicitly programmed.\", 1959</string>
    <string name="page_1_1_definition_author">- Arthur Samuel</string>
    <string name="page_1_2_definition">\"<b>Machine Learning:</b> A computer program is said to learn from experience <b>E</b>, with respect to some task <b>T</b>, and some performance measure <b>P</b>, if its performance on <b>T</b> as measured by <b>P</b> improves with experience <b>E</b>. \", 1997</string>
    <string name="page_1_2_definition_author">- Tom mitchell</string>
    <string name="page_1_4_supervised"><b>Supervised Learning.</b>  The algorithm is given training data which contains the "correct answer" for each example.</string>
    <string name="page_1_4_unsupervised"><b>Unsupervised Learning.</b>  The algorithm looks for structure in the training data, like finding which examples are similar to each other, and group them in clusters. </string>
    <string name="page_1_3_text_1">The task <b>T</b> of that system is to flag credit card transactions as fraudulent or not.  The performance measure <b>P</b> could be the percentage of fraudulent transactions that are detected.</string>
    <string name="page_1_3_text_2">The system learns if the percentage of fraudulent transactions that are detected increases over time.  Here the experience E is the set of already processed transaction records.  Once a transaction is processed, then we know if it is a fraud or not, and we can feed that information to the system for it learn.</string>
    <string name="page_1_3_text_3">Once a transaction is processed, then we know if it is a fraud or not, and we can feed that information to the system for it learn.</string>

    <string name="upcoming_badge">Upcoming Badge</string>
    <string name="your_badge">Your Badge</string>

</resources>
